http://www.breakpoint.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
The Colson Center for Christian Worldview Privacy Policy
The Colson Center (“TCC” or “we”) has adopted the privacy policy outlined in this document applicable to all of our websites and mobile apps.  This Policy informs you how we collect, use and share the personally identifiable information we obtain from and about you. This Policy applies only to information collected on our Sites and not to information collected offline. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any web site not operated by TCC to which our Sites link or that links to our Sites.
Information The Colson Center Collects and Receives
TCC collects and retains information about you and your device when you visit our website or apps or when you give us information through the Colson Center websites or mobile apps.  We use this information to better serve the needs of the ministry and the ministry’s digital assets.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
When your computer or mobile device connects to our web sites and apps, our systems collect and monitor user information and behavior on how our sites are utilized. We use third party services as well as our own to create an anonymous profile that is established based on your visit and information such as the frequency and length of your visit, and browser type. As with most sites, we automatically recognize and log the Internet URL from which you access our Sites. We may also log your Internet protocol address or “IP address” (which may indicate the general location of your computer on the Internet), Internet service provider, and date/time stamp. Log files are used primarily for system administration and troubleshooting purposes.
Personally Identifiable Information
We collect personal information from you, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, and email address from a variety of sources, including what you voluntarily provide to us. Once we have this information, any previous anonymous profile associated with your IP address is updated with your personal information, including email address, and your email becomes the primary identifier for your profile.
How We Use Your Information
The information we collect is used to improve your Colson Center experience. Visitors are provided services and content tailored especially for them or their geographic area.  Occasionally, The Colson Center conducts user surveys to better target the content we provide.  These surveys require the user to sign up and opt in to be able to take part.
The Colson Center employs strict security measures to safeguard online transactions, and personal information is stored in a secure database and always sent via an encrypted channel.  Our third party services and vendors utilize additional strict measures to safeguard personal information that we use on their platforms.
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to connect you with articles newsletters, marketing or promotional materials for events and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of any, or all, of these communications by following the unsubscribe link on each email we send.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 23, 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Additional Information
The Colson Center Privacy Policy was updated effective 3/23/2018. Cookies are text files that are placed in your device’s browser and are used to help recognize your browser across different web pages, websites, and browsing sessions. Cookies are stored on your device. We may use cookies together with other information to enhance and personalize your experience on our Services (or elsewhere online), including:
to remember your preferences and registration information
to measure and research the effectiveness of our services and communications
to customize the content to fit your geographical preferences
In Summary
TCC is committed to protecting the privacy of any user who visits our websites and mobile apps. The information we collect is used to enhance your overall experience.  We do not  and will not sell, trade, or rent or giveaway your personal information to anyone.
CONTACT INFORMATION
The Colson Center for Christian Worldview
P.O. Box 62160
Colorado Springs, CO 80962
General Information
1-877-322-5527
Listen
All Audio
What Would You Say?
Store
Colson Center Store
Connect
Contact Us
© Copyright 2020, All Rights Reserved.
What Would You Say?
